My name is Blessing Iloanya. I'm from Anambra State.
I'm a civil servant.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN is that
I am addicted to sniffing and drinking kerosene.
I'm going to prove that it is kerosene. I'm going to burn this piece of wood.
Wow, my God!
My God!
Kerosene
That's kerosene indeed.
The woman beside me is my mum.
It all started about 18 years ago when I was in secondary school.
There was this particular day when a thought came to me
that this kerosene would be nice, I should try it.
So, I cut a piece of paper, soaked it into the kerosene and started sniffing it.
From sniffing the kerosene, I started sucking and drinking it.
From there, I started taking it every day.
Then, I discovered that to enjoy it more, I would go and buy biscuits and soak them in the kerosene.
Viewers, I hope you are watching.
Viewers, all over the world, are you watching?
Wow.
Woman Eating A Biscuit Dipped Into Kerosene
If you know that solution has come for you, raise up your hand!
Your own passes kerosene?
[No!]
It usually tastes very nice. I enjoy it.
I have tried on my own to stop it.
I tried to keep kerosene away from anywhere I stay but every time I would see it,
I would dip my hand into it and begin to sniff it and put it in my mouth
Blessing dips the tissue into the kerosene to demonstrate how she sniffs and drinks it.
She continues to suck all the kerosene out of the tissue and swallows it.
This is one of the methods she uses to consume the kerosene.
I take it every day but I've tried to stop it on my own;
I tried to keep kerosene away from my house.
Since how many years now?
For 18 years now.
You have tried all.
Yes, I've tried on my own; I´ve prayed but it's not working.
Man of God, it has affected my life in so many ways.
Most times when I take it, my stomach would be upset.
I would begin to to go to the toilet very often.
My life is full of hardship and disappointment.
Who has Anointing Water?
A man steps forward.
You just watch.
In the name of Jesus Christ of Nazareth, I command you out, in Jesus' name!
You spirit of killing, stealing and destruction, in the name of Jesus Christ, out!
Jesus is greater than you!
Out, in the name of Jesus!
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Now, she is free.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
What happened when he was spraying the Anointing Water?
I was feeling some kind of sensation inside me.
Blessing takes the tissue and dips it once again into the kerosene to observe if truly she is delivered.
To God be the glory! Blessing is finally delivered!
Set Free In Jesus' Name
You are now a normal human being. This is what is supposed to happen.
If you go home now, if you take kerosene,
even if you perceive the odour of kerosene, you will cough.
This is a normal human being now.
What happened?
It's irritating.
Okay, what happened? Why are you coughing?
It is the irritation that is making me cough.
She has been drinking it for the past 18 years and she never coughed.
The little she has just taken now, she is vomiting it which is normal for a human being.
That shows that this woman was not normal before.
She is just getting normal now.
Do you see?
What has happened to you?
The taste is not okay anymore. I hate the taste.
My system is irritated.
To God be the glory! Blessing is finally delivered.
She applies a hand washing product to remove the kerosene from her hands.
On the left, we witness the burning of real kerosene -
the product Blessing had an addiction for, for the past 18 years.
On the right, Blessing uses mouthwash to get rid of the taste that now irritates her after her deliverance.
On the left, we also saw the demonstration of the different methods
Blessing formerly used to consume kerosene on a daily basis.
Sniffing it profusely with a tissue and drinking it time and time again
until all the kerosene had been completely drained out of it.
She also dipped biscuits into the kerosene as to soak the kerosene in the biscuit
and then consume it without any hesitation.
These are just some of the ways she had consumed kerosene for the past 18 years.
Indeed, this was not normal.
This was the work of evil spirits.
But to God be the glory, she received her deliverance and her 18-year hazardous habit
of sniffing and drinking kerosene was put to an end by the author of life - Jesus Christ!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Good morning, Church!
My name is Blessing Ezekwudo and the man standing by my side is my husband
and the little girl is my daughter Akuchi.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
The lady you saw over there was me.
Six years ago, I was addicted to sniffing and drinking kerosene.
It was so bad that even when I went out,
I would want to run back to the house so that I could continue with my acts.
Most times, the sniffing would not be enough.
I would want to drink it and I would want something that would go with it.
I would go and buy biscuits. I would soak it into the kerosene.
Before I would know it, I would be chewing and enjoying it.
After that, I would not eat much food and go to bed.
it continued and continued. My family knew all about it because I couldn't hide it anymore.
There was nothing they could do about it.
I tried stopping on my own but it was not possible.
I tried, prayed and everything. I couldn't stop it.
When I saw so many people being delivered on Emmanuel TV of all manner of addictions,
I said to myself, "I have to go there so that this habit can stop".
So I came here in January 2012.
The man of God asked somebody to minister the Anointing Water on me.
That was done and I was delivered.
My brothers and sisters, after that, the love, the passion for kerosene died.
Whenever I saw it, I hated it.
Two months after that, I met my husband and we got married.
After that, I had a child. Praise the Lord!
Praise the Lord!
So, ma'am, can you tell us - what were the challenges when you were still having
that addiction to drinking and sniffing kerosene at that time?
The challenges I was passing through were: I always wanted to be on my own.
I was kind of isolated from people because it was not normal.
I thought I was hiding it.
I always wanted to be on my own so I would be able to continue with that act.
Beside that, I was always having stomach aches.
My health was affected.
Your deliverance shows that your prayers for many years are not lost.
Jesus Christ has answered your prayers through this medium of the New Morning Water.
What can you say about the medium of the Morning Water that God used to deliver you?
The medium of the Morning Water is like the blood of Jesus.
When I was sprayed with the Morning Water, I had a current run all over me, like a fire.
In fact, it´s the answer for today.
Amen. Indeed, Jesus Christ uses this medium to bring about healing,
deliverance and all of God's blessings in the lives of his people.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Good Morning, Church.
I just came here to appreciate the Lord
for the deliverance of my wife prior to our marriage.
When we were preparing (to get married) and all that, she explained to me
that this was the case she had gone through for several years.
She visited The SCOAN and God in His infinite mercy visited and delivered her
from that affliction of 18 years as we could see.
We indeed got married.
There was no such issue in our life and she is perfectly okay.
Praise the Lord! Clap for Jesus Christ!
What is the message that you have for people out there who are suffering from a similar condition?
Children of God, whenever you are passing through any challenge, no matter what it is,
the best thing to do at that time is to run to God through Jesus
because he said in Romans 8:32 that He didn't spare His son but gave Him freely.
Shall He not give us anything that we desire?
Is it deliverance that you need? Is it breakthrough? Is it healing?
The best person to run to is God through Jesus who can deliver you
or give you anything you desire at that point. Praise the Lord!
TT: J Margaret Fernandez 11/6/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 08/07/2018